What is your challenge within
Replit today?  It will always be figuring out the
next version of Agent and what
exactly to do with the right roadmap,
especially since we now see that we launch
a new version about every 6 months.   I do
n't know if it will always be like this, but for now it
's working pretty well.  It gives us
this cadence of not always making
small increments that then don't
help you think about the big picture and
so every now and then I stop everyone, say "Okay,
whiteboard," I write maybe a
10-page document, I describe what the
next version of Agent will be like and we dive in
and build it and
launch it within a few months.
That's always the biggest challenge
because I always have to predict whether the models
will be powerful enough to get there,
whether it will be cheap enough, whether it will be
fast enough.  There are a lot of
different dimensions that need to be
optimized.
Of course, you have to design for
future models that haven't come out yet.
Clear?
What are you working on now?  What
challenges are you currently
facing?  We've already taken the
necessary step to actually start from
a very detailed prompt and build
a complete zero-to-one application
.  What's still missing from
the experience is actually opening
your WhatsApp, asking Replet to
do something that doesn't
necessarily have to create an app, but is a
task that among the various things it requires
perhaps needs to create an app that
connects to your HubSpot, then create an
automation, email your customer, therefore
an entire workflow and rather than
having to build all the pieces by hand,
you give us a high-level idea of ​​what
you want to do, we build everything
you need, we get back to you when
everything is ready and maybe we
even let you run it
independently.